 export const geography =  [
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20European%20country%20is%20not%20a%20part%20of%20the%20EU%3F",
"correct_answer": "Norway",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Lithuania",
"Ireland",
"Czechia"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20state%20of%20the%20United%20States%20is%20the%20smallest%3F",
"correct_answer": "Rhode%20Island%20",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Maine",
"Vermont",
"Massachusetts"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "On%20a%20London%20Underground%20map%2C%20what%20colour%20is%20the%20Circle%20Line%3F",
"correct_answer": "Yellow",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Red",
"Blue",
"Green"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20former%20country%20that%20was%20succeeded%20by%20countries%20such%20as%20Serbia%2C%20Croatia%20and%20Slovenia%3F",
"correct_answer": "Yugoslavia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Czechoslovakia",
"Abkhazia",
"South%20Ossetia"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20countries%20is%20%22doubly%20landlocked%22%20%28surrounded%20entirely%20by%20one%20or%20more%20landlocked%20countries%29%3F",
"correct_answer": "Uzbekistan",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Switzerland",
"Bolivia",
"Ethiopia"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Chile%3F",
"correct_answer": "Santiago",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Valpara%C3%ADso",
"Copiap%C3%B3",
"Antofagasta"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20capital%20of%20Turkey%3F",
"correct_answer": "Ankara",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Istanbul",
"Izmir",
"Bursa"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20are%20the%20four%20corner%20states%20of%20the%20US%3F",
"correct_answer": "Utah%2C%20Colorado%2C%20Arizona%2C%20New%20Mexico",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Oregon%2C%20Idaho%2C%20Nevada%2C%20Utah",
"Kansas%2C%20Oklahoma%2C%20Arkansas%2C%20Louisiana",
"South%20Dakota%2C%20Minnesota%2C%20Nebraska%2C%20Iowa"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Kuala%20Lumpur%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20which%20country%3F",
"correct_answer": "Malaysia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Indonesia",
"Singapore",
"Thailand"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20countries%20is%20within%20the%20Eurozone%20but%20outside%20of%20the%20Schengen%20Area%3F",
"correct_answer": "Cyprus",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Malta",
"Greece",
"Portugal"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20land%20of%20Gotland%20is%20located%20in%20which%20European%20country%3F",
"correct_answer": "Sweden",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Denmark",
"Norway",
"Germany"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20countries%20does%20NOT%20recognize%20Armenia%20as%20an%20independent%20country%3F",
"correct_answer": "Pakistan",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Iran",
"Turkey",
"Azerbaijan"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20countries%20banned%20the%20use%20of%20personal%20genetic%20ancestry%20tests%3F",
"correct_answer": "Germany",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Austria",
"Canada",
"Sweden"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "On%20which%20continent%20is%20the%20country%20of%20Angola%20located%3F",
"correct_answer": "Africa",
"incorrect_answers": [
"South%20America",
"Europe",
"Asia"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20African%20country%20has%20Portuguese%20as%20its%20official%20language%3F",
"correct_answer": "Mozambique",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Botswana",
"Gabon",
"Togo"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Where%20is%20the%20area%20commonly%20known%20as%20the%20Bermuda%20Triangle%3F",
"correct_answer": "North%20Atlantic%20Ocean%2C%20between%20Florida%20and%20Puerto%20Rico",
"incorrect_answers": [
"North%20Pacific%20Ocean%2C%20between%20Japan%20and%20the%20USA",
"In%20the%20Caribbean%20Sea",
"South%20Pacific%20Ocean%2C%20far%20off%20Chile"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20World%20Health%20Organization%20headquarters%20is%20located%20in%20which%20European%20country%3F",
"correct_answer": "Switzerland",
"incorrect_answers": [
"United%20Kingdom",
"France",
"Belgium"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20the%20State%20of%20Washington%2C%20United%20States%3F",
"correct_answer": "Olympia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Washington%20D.C.",
"Seattle",
"Yukon"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20event%20led%20to%20Liechenstein%20adding%20a%20crown%20to%20its%20flag%3F",
"correct_answer": "The%201936%20Olympics",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Coronation%20of%20Prince%20Johann%20I%20Joseph%20in%201805",
"Charles%20VI%27s%20decree%20in%201719",
"Signing%20of%20the%201862%20Constitution%20of%20Liechtenstein"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20country%20has%20three%20capital%20cities%3F",
"correct_answer": "South%20Africa",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Somalia",
"China",
"United%20Kingdom"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20country%20has%20the%20abbreviation%20%22CH%22%3F",
"correct_answer": "Switzerland",
"incorrect_answers": [
"China",
"Canada",
"No%20Country"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20tall%20is%20One%20World%20Trade%20Center%20in%20New%20York%20City%3F",
"correct_answer": "1%2C776%20ft",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1%2C888%20ft",
"1%2C225%20ft",
"1%2C960%20ft"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20largest%20Muslim%20country%20in%20the%20world%3F",
"correct_answer": "Indonesia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Pakistan",
"Saudi%20Arabia",
"Iran"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20Canadian%20province%20has%20Charlottetown%20as%20its%20capital%3F",
"correct_answer": "Prince%20Edward%20Island",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Saskachewan",
"Northwest%20Terrirories",
"Ontario"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20British%20Columbia%2C%20Canada%3F",
"correct_answer": "Victoria",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Vancouver",
"Hope",
"Kelowna"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20one%20of%20these%20countries%20borders%20with%20Poland%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lithuania",
"incorrect_answers": [
"France",
"Norway",
"Netherlands"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Belarus%3F",
"correct_answer": "Minsk",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Warsaw",
"Kiev",
"Vilnius"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20land%20mass%20of%20modern%20day%20Turkey%20is%20called%20what%3F",
"correct_answer": "Anatolia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Ismuth%20of%20Ottoma",
"Ottoma",
"Ismuth%20of%20Anatolia"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20timezones%20does%20Russia%20have%3F",
"correct_answer": "11",
"incorrect_answers": [
"6",
"24",
"16"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20the%202016%20Global%20Peace%20Index%20poll%2C%20out%20of%20163%20countries%2C%20what%20was%20the%20United%20States%20of%20America%20ranked%3F",
"correct_answer": "103",
"incorrect_answers": [
"10",
"59",
"79"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20highest%20mountain%20in%20the%20world%3F",
"correct_answer": "Mt.%20Everest",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Mount%20Godwin%20Austen",
"Kangchenjunga",
"Annapurna"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20region%20conjoining%20Pakistan%2C%20India%2C%20and%20China%20with%20unknown%20leadership%20called%3F",
"correct_answer": "Kashmir",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Andorra",
"Gibraltar",
"Quin"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Estonia%3F",
"correct_answer": "Tallinn",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Helsinki",
"Tartu",
"Riga"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20fifth%20largest%20country%20by%20area%3F",
"correct_answer": "Brazil",
"incorrect_answers": [
"United%20States",
"Australia",
"India"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20independent%20countries%20are%20there%20within%20the%20continent%20of%20South%20America%3F",
"correct_answer": "12",
"incorrect_answers": [
"8",
"9",
"10"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20continent%20is%20the%20country%20Lesotho%20in%3F",
"correct_answer": "Africa",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Asia",
"South%20America",
"Europe"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20is%20the%20longest%20river%20in%20Europe%3F",
"correct_answer": "Volga",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Danube",
"Ural",
"Dnieper"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20country%27s%20capitals%20starts%20with%20the%20letter%20B%3F",
"correct_answer": "Lebanon",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jordan",
"Kuwait",
"Qatar"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20English%20county%20will%20you%20find%20the%20University%20of%20East%20Anglia%3F",
"correct_answer": "Norfolk",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Suffolk",
"Essex",
"Cambridgeshire"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20official%20national%20language%20of%20Pakistan%3F",
"correct_answer": "Urdu",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Indian",
"Punjabi",
"Pashto"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20only%20remaining%20Grand%20Duchy%20in%20the%20world%20%3F",
"correct_answer": "Luxembourg",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Montenegro",
"Liechtenstein",
"Andorra"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20northernmost%20human%20settlement%20with%20year%20round%20inhabitants%3F",
"correct_answer": "Alert%2C%20Canada",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Nagurskoye%2C%20Russia",
"McMurdo%20Station%2C%20Antarctica%20",
"Honningsv%C3%A5g%2C%20Norway"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20capital%20of%20Greenland%3F",
"correct_answer": "Nuuk",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Sisimiut",
"Narsaq",
"Maniitsoq"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20provinces%20are%20in%20the%20Netherlands%3F",
"correct_answer": "12",
"incorrect_answers": [
"14",
"10",
"13"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Where%20is%20Hadrian%27s%20Wall%20located%3F",
"correct_answer": "Carlisle%2C%20England",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Rome%2C%20Italy",
"Alexandria%2C%20Egypt",
"Dublin%2C%20Ireland"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20mountain%20range%20lines%20the%20border%20between%20Spain%20and%20France%3F",
"correct_answer": "Pyrenees",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Alps",
"Carpathians",
"Urals"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Lake%20Titicaca%20is%20located%20between%20which%20two%20nations%3F",
"correct_answer": "Peru%20and%20Bolivia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Kenya%20and%20Uganda",
"Mexico%20and%20the%20United%20States",
"India%20and%20Bangladesh"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20Pyrenees%20mountains%20are%20located%20on%20the%20border%20of%20which%20two%20countries%3F",
"correct_answer": "France%20and%20Spain",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Italy%20and%20Switzerland",
"Norway%20and%20Sweden",
"Russia%20and%20Ukraine"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20was%20the%20African%20nation%20of%20Zimbabwe%20formerly%20known%20as%3F",
"correct_answer": "Rhodesia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Zambia",
"Mozambique",
"%20Bulawayo"
]
},
{
"category": "Geography",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20formerly%20East-Prussian%20city%20of%20K%C3%B6nigsberg%20is%20known%20as%20which%20Russian%20City%20today%3F",
"correct_answer": "Kaliningrad",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Kazan",
"Kursk",
"Krasnodar"
]
}
]